{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906367360","data":{"timestamp":" 946906367359"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" c530a506-5432-43a7-8c07-5d01a15e280e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906369556","data":{"timestamp":" 946906369555"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" c530a506-5432-43a7-8c07-5d01a15e280e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_4_0-4-13"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906395628","data":{"timestamp":" 946906395628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 8419865c-dacd-4eac-b2ae-ae4de920862c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zawadi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" ZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-Z.rand.63","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906396556","data":{"timestamp":" 946906396556"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 8419865c-dacd-4eac-b2ae-ae4de920862c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" zawadi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906396635","data":{"timestamp":" 946906396634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 8419865c-dacd-4eac-b2ae-ae4de920862c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-Z.rand.63"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zawadi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAWADI"," userResponse":" ZAWADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906407497","data":{"timestamp":" 946906407497"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGOE"," userResponse":" KIGOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906408129","data":{"timestamp":" 946906408128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906408325","data":{"timestamp":" 946906408325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906409227","data":{"timestamp":" 946906409226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZEA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906409840","data":{"timestamp":" 946906409840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENISI"," userResponse":" TENISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906410813","data":{"timestamp":" 946906410813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kigoe changu cha kuchezea tenisi kimepotea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEPOTEA"," userResponse":" KIMEPOTEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906413251","data":{"timestamp":" 946906413251"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906413995","data":{"timestamp":" 946906413995"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMEENDA"," userResponse":" KIMEENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906414627","data":{"timestamp":" 946906414627"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui kimeenda wapi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906418641","data":{"timestamp":" 946906418640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906419044","data":{"timestamp":" 946906419043"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906419268","data":{"timestamp":" 946906419268"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906419931","data":{"timestamp":" 946906419930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906422626","data":{"timestamp":" 946906422626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906423720","data":{"timestamp":" 946906423720"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906427277","data":{"timestamp":" 946906427277"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906427548","data":{"timestamp":" 946906427548"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906427741","data":{"timestamp":" 946906427740"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906428483","data":{"timestamp":" 946906428483"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta juu ya kabati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABATI"," userResponse":" KABATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906431034","data":{"timestamp":" 946906431034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906432128","data":{"timestamp":" 946906432127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906435907","data":{"timestamp":" 946906435907"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906436290","data":{"timestamp":" 946906436290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906436383","data":{"timestamp":" 946906436383"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906437098","data":{"timestamp":" 946906437097"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta chini ya kitanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906439542","data":{"timestamp":" 946906439542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906439945","data":{"timestamp":" 946906439945"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906440938","data":{"timestamp":" 946906440938"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hata hapo sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906444305","data":{"timestamp":" 946906444305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906444706","data":{"timestamp":" 946906444706"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906444772","data":{"timestamp":" 946906444771"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906445501","data":{"timestamp":" 946906445501"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta ndani ya sanduku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANDUKU"," userResponse":" SANDUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906447966","data":{"timestamp":" 946906447966"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906448755","data":{"timestamp":" 946906448755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAPAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906448974","data":{"timestamp":" 946906448974"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906449662","data":{"timestamp":" 946906449662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DALILI"," userResponse":" DALILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906449987","data":{"timestamp":" 946906449986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906450501","data":{"timestamp":" 946906450500"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapakuwa na dalili yake pale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906454125","data":{"timestamp":" 946906454125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIKITAFUTA"," userResponse":" NILIKITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906454708","data":{"timestamp":" 946906454708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906455116","data":{"timestamp":" 946906455116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nilikitafuta katika dari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DARI"," userResponse":" DARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906458547","data":{"timestamp":" 946906458546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILIANGALIA"," userResponse":" NILIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906459301","data":{"timestamp":" 946906459301"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906459764","data":{"timestamp":" 946906459764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906460337","data":{"timestamp":" 946906460337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906461538","data":{"timestamp":" 946906461538"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAANGALIA"," userResponse":" NIKAANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906462173","data":{"timestamp":" 946906462172"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906462766","data":{"timestamp":" 946906462765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niliangalia hapa na pale nikaangalia kila mahali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAHALI"," userResponse":" MAHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906465384","data":{"timestamp":" 946906465384"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906466499","data":{"timestamp":" 946906466498"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906473649","data":{"timestamp":" 946906473648"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906473737","data":{"timestamp":" 946906473737"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 51d53b7c-4917-4c3f-9888-f5b04f0c821a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906484264","data":{"timestamp":" 946906484263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 695234e2-1231-4f1b-97e7-24f85178fc92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-t"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906487948","data":{"timestamp":" 946906487948"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 695234e2-1231-4f1b-97e7-24f85178fc92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_ch-e-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906489664","data":{"timestamp":" 946906489664"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 695234e2-1231-4f1b-97e7-24f85178fc92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_ch-e-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906499207","data":{"timestamp":" 946906499206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 695234e2-1231-4f1b-97e7-24f85178fc92"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.rand.all.stat.show.124"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_z_ch-e-z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906513780","data":{"timestamp":" 946906513780"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 9847cbab-c151-4d7e-9674-518cd6825934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906518989","data":{"timestamp":" 946906518989"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 9847cbab-c151-4d7e-9674-518cd6825934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906522430","data":{"timestamp":" 946906522429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 9847cbab-c151-4d7e-9674-518cd6825934"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_10_3-10-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906543091","data":{"timestamp":" 946906543091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_z_r"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906549782","data":{"timestamp":" 946906549782"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_y_z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906556397","data":{"timestamp":" 946906556396"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_g_h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906563066","data":{"timestamp":" 946906563066"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_g_p"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906569725","data":{"timestamp":" 946906569725"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_l_r"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906577205","data":{"timestamp":" 946906577204"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_l_r"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906583884","data":{"timestamp":" 946906583883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_s_z_y"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906590523","data":{"timestamp":" 946906590523"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_z_y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906597985","data":{"timestamp":" 946906597985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_z_y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906608368","data":{"timestamp":" 946906608368"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_z_y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906615009","data":{"timestamp":" 946906615009"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_w_l_z"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906621636","data":{"timestamp":" 946906621636"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_b_ch_z"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906628264","data":{"timestamp":" 946906628264"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_k_j_z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906641424","data":{"timestamp":" 946906641424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7be7287a-f200-4bf7-9727-a666867c0f3b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_Z..Z.all.10.rand.say.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_k_j_z"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906652557","data":{"timestamp":" 946906652557"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906653171","data":{"timestamp":" 946906653170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906653400","data":{"timestamp":" 946906653400"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906654023","data":{"timestamp":" 946906654022"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906654815","data":{"timestamp":" 946906654814"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIA"," userResponse":" DUNIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906655816","data":{"timestamp":" 946906655815"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906656455","data":{"timestamp":" 946906656454"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906657628","data":{"timestamp":" 946906657628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906658371","data":{"timestamp":" 946906658370"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUBWA"," userResponse":" MIKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906659605","data":{"timestamp":" 946906659604"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIFUNIKA"," userResponse":" ILIFUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906660407","data":{"timestamp":" 946906660407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" ULIMWENGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906660882","data":{"timestamp":" 946906660882"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906661815","data":{"timestamp":" 946906661814"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale dunia ilipokuwa mpya milima mikubwa ilifunika ulimwengu kama blanketi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BLANKETI"," userResponse":" BLANKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906664150","data":{"timestamp":" 946906664150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906664641","data":{"timestamp":" 946906664640"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906665393","data":{"timestamp":" 946906665392"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906666620","data":{"timestamp":" 946906666617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILICHONGOKA"," userResponse":" ILICHONGOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906667744","data":{"timestamp":" 946906667743"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nayo miti mirefu ilichongoka mawinguni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGUNI"," userResponse":" MAWINGUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906671104","data":{"timestamp":" 946906671104"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNIANI"," userResponse":" DUNIANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906671953","data":{"timestamp":" 946906671952"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906672215","data":{"timestamp":" 946906672214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906672796","data":{"timestamp":" 946906672795"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906673338","data":{"timestamp":" 946906673337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906673558","data":{"timestamp":" 946906673558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906674147","data":{"timestamp":" 946906674146"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906674970","data":{"timestamp":" 946906674969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906675915","data":{"timestamp":" 946906675914"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHADIDI"," userResponse":" SHADIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906676144","data":{"timestamp":" 946906676144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906677496","data":{"timestamp":" 946906677496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILILOTULIA"," userResponse":" LILILOTULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906678467","data":{"timestamp":" 946906678467"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Duniani palikuwa na dimbwi kubwa la maji baridi shadidi na lililotulia tuli."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TULI"," userResponse":" TULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906680791","data":{"timestamp":" 946906680791"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906681450","data":{"timestamp":" 946906681449"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906682263","data":{"timestamp":" 946906682263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906683336","data":{"timestamp":" 946906683335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIREFU"," userResponse":" KIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906684061","data":{"timestamp":" 946906684060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906685295","data":{"timestamp":" 946906685295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIGUBIKWA"," userResponse":" LILIGUBIKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906685509","data":{"timestamp":" 946906685509"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906686038","data":{"timestamp":" 946906686037"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906687043","data":{"timestamp":" 946906687042"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kina chake kilikuwa kirefu na liligubikwa na giza totoro."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOTORO"," userResponse":" TOTORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906689976","data":{"timestamp":" 946906689976"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906690942","data":{"timestamp":" 946906690942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAKAFU"," userResponse":" SAKAFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906691224","data":{"timestamp":" 946906691224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906691970","data":{"timestamp":" 946906691970"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906692625","data":{"timestamp":" 946906692624"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906693599","data":{"timestamp":" 946906693599"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIISHI"," userResponse":" PALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906694451","data":{"timestamp":" 946906694451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906695021","data":{"timestamp":" 946906695020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwenye sakafu ya dimbwi hilo paliishi nyoka wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906697602","data":{"timestamp":" 946906697602"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906698522","data":{"timestamp":" 946906698521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906699474","data":{"timestamp":" 946906699474"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNENE"," userResponse":" MNENE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906700143","data":{"timestamp":" 946906700143"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906700665","data":{"timestamp":" 946906700665"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906701247","data":{"timestamp":" 946906701246"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja alikuwa mnene na mwenye nguvu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906703440","data":{"timestamp":" 946906703440"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906704317","data":{"timestamp":" 946906704316"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENGINE"," userResponse":" MWENGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906705325","data":{"timestamp":" 946906705325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906705590","data":{"timestamp":" 946906705590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906706115","data":{"timestamp":" 946906706115"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBO"," userResponse":" UMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906706884","data":{"timestamp":" 946906706883"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906707032","data":{"timestamp":" 946906707031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906708112","data":{"timestamp":" 946906708111"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUVUTIA"," userResponse":" KUVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906708668","data":{"timestamp":" 946906708668"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906709390","data":{"timestamp":" 946906709389"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mwengine alikuwa na umbo dogo la kuvutia na dhaifu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHAIFU"," userResponse":" DHAIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906712392","data":{"timestamp":" 946906712391"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906713138","data":{"timestamp":" 946906713137"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906713647","data":{"timestamp":" 946906713647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906714750","data":{"timestamp":" 946906714749"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKATOKEA"," userResponse":" PAKATOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906715683","data":{"timestamp":" 946906715683"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DHORUBA"," userResponse":" DHORUBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906716303","data":{"timestamp":" 946906716303"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Basi siku moja pakatokea dhoruba kubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906718863","data":{"timestamp":" 946906718863"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906719719","data":{"timestamp":" 946906719718"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPIGA"," userResponse":" ILIPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906719938","data":{"timestamp":" 946906719938"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906720705","data":{"timestamp":" 946906720705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENYA"," userResponse":" KUPENYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906721256","data":{"timestamp":" 946906721255"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906721861","data":{"timestamp":" 946906721860"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906722061","data":{"timestamp":" 946906722061"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906722702","data":{"timestamp":" 946906722702"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906725251","data":{"timestamp":" 946906725251"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906726433","data":{"timestamp":" 946906726432"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKAGAWIKA"," userResponse":" YAKAGAWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906726735","data":{"timestamp":" 946906726735"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906727206","data":{"timestamp":" 946906727206"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906727932","data":{"timestamp":" 946906727932"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906728756","data":{"timestamp":" 946906728755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906729343","data":{"timestamp":" 946906729343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906730128","data":{"timestamp":" 946906730128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWEZA"," userResponse":" WAKAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906730732","data":{"timestamp":" 946906730732"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906731357","data":{"timestamp":" 946906731356"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906731992","data":{"timestamp":" 946906731992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906732626","data":{"timestamp":" 946906732626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maji yakagawika kwa muda mfupi wale nyoka wakaweza kuona ardhi kule juu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906735489","data":{"timestamp":" 946906735488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906736036","data":{"timestamp":" 946906736035"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906736345","data":{"timestamp":" 946906736345"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906736977","data":{"timestamp":" 946906736977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906737633","data":{"timestamp":" 946906737632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906737888","data":{"timestamp":" 946906737887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906738448","data":{"timestamp":" 946906738447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYENYE"," userResponse":" VYENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906739163","data":{"timestamp":" 946906739163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUMBO"," userResponse":" MAUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906740137","data":{"timestamp":" 946906740137"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906741193","data":{"timestamp":" 946906741193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906743937","data":{"timestamp":" 946906743937"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIONA"," userResponse":" WALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906744845","data":{"timestamp":" 946906744844"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIUMBE"," userResponse":" VIUMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906745425","data":{"timestamp":" 946906745424"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WENYE"," userResponse":" WENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906746038","data":{"timestamp":" 946906746037"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906746920","data":{"timestamp":" 946906746920"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906749241","data":{"timestamp":" 946906749241"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906749796","data":{"timestamp":" 946906749795"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906751075","data":{"timestamp":" 946906751073"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALICHOONA"," userResponse":" WALICHOONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906751934","data":{"timestamp":" 946906751934"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHINI"," userResponse":" ARDHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906753118","data":{"timestamp":" 946906753118"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIVUTIA"," userResponse":" KILIVUTIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906753722","data":{"timestamp":" 946906753721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila kitu walichoona ardhini kilivutia sana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906756204","data":{"timestamp":" 946906756204"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906756654","data":{"timestamp":" 946906756654"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906758100","data":{"timestamp":" 946906758100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIPORUDIANA"," userResponse":" YALIPORUDIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906758696","data":{"timestamp":" 946906758696"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906759558","data":{"timestamp":" 946906759558"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906760127","data":{"timestamp":" 946906760127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906761380","data":{"timestamp":" 946906761377"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIENDELEA"," userResponse":" WALIENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906762481","data":{"timestamp":" 946906762481"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" KUKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906763242","data":{"timestamp":" 946906763242"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZURI"," userResponse":" UZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906764315","data":{"timestamp":" 946906764315"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIOKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906765226","data":{"timestamp":" 946906765225"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati maji yaliporudiana tena wale nyoka waliendelea kukumbuka uzuri waliokuwa wameona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEONA"," userResponse":" WAMEONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906768567","data":{"timestamp":" 946906768566"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUWEZI"," userResponse":" HATUWEZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906769525","data":{"timestamp":" 946906769524"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUENDELEA"," userResponse":" KUENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906770227","data":{"timestamp":" 946906770226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906770656","data":{"timestamp":" 946906770655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906771203","data":{"timestamp":" 946906771202"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIMBWI"," userResponse":" DIMBWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906771623","data":{"timestamp":" 946906771623"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906772121","data":{"timestamp":" 946906772121"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LENYE"," userResponse":" LENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906772833","data":{"timestamp":" 946906772833"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906773118","data":{"timestamp":" 946906773118"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906774223","data":{"timestamp":" 946906774223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906775801","data":{"timestamp":" 946906775801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMBIANA"," userResponse":" WALIAMBIANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906778064","data":{"timestamp":" 946906778064"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906778488","data":{"timestamp":" 946906778488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906778929","data":{"timestamp":" 946906778929"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906779953","data":{"timestamp":" 946906779952"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUKAIONE"," userResponse":" TUKAIONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906780737","data":{"timestamp":" 946906780737"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twende kule juu tukaione ardhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906783851","data":{"timestamp":" 946906783850"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAWEZAJE"," userResponse":" TUTAWEZAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906784476","data":{"timestamp":" 946906784476"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906785020","data":{"timestamp":" 946906785019"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906785903","data":{"timestamp":" 946906785902"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ARDHI"," userResponse":" ARDHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906788171","data":{"timestamp":" 946906788171"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906788593","data":{"timestamp":" 946906788592"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906789236","data":{"timestamp":" 946906789236"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906790328","data":{"timestamp":" 946906790328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906792540","data":{"timestamp":" 946906792540"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906794331","data":{"timestamp":" 946906794331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" TUTATAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906794614","data":{"timestamp":" 946906794614"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906795648","data":{"timestamp":" 946906795647"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je tutatambaa kwa matumbo?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUMBO"," userResponse":" MATUMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906798556","data":{"timestamp":" 946906798556"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906798723","data":{"timestamp":" 946906798723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906799577","data":{"timestamp":" 946906799576"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906801017","data":{"timestamp":" 946906801017"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," userResponse":" HAWATATUCHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906801225","data":{"timestamp":" 946906801225"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906802111","data":{"timestamp":" 946906802111"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUONA"," userResponse":" KUTUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906802738","data":{"timestamp":" 946906802738"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUNI"," userResponse":" DUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906803918","data":{"timestamp":" 946906803918"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906804832","data":{"timestamp":" 946906804831"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege wa angani hawatatucheka na kutuona duni mwenzake alimjibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIMJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906808495","data":{"timestamp":" 946906808494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutatambaa tutatembea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATUTATAMBAA"," userResponse":" HATUTATAMBAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906810448","data":{"timestamp":" 946906810448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hatutatambaa tutatembea!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTATEMBEA"," userResponse":" TUTATEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906812984","data":{"timestamp":" 946906812984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906813526","data":{"timestamp":" 946906813526"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAO"," userResponse":" HAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906814957","data":{"timestamp":" 946906814956"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIJIKUNJUA"," userResponse":" WALIJIKUNJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906816499","data":{"timestamp":" 946906816499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nyoka hao walijikunjua polepole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLEPOLE"," userResponse":" POLEPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906819482","data":{"timestamp":" 946906819482"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAANZA"," userResponse":" WAKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906820696","data":{"timestamp":" 946906820695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906820965","data":{"timestamp":" 946906820965"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906822238","data":{"timestamp":" 946906822238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906823619","data":{"timestamp":" 946906823619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" WAKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906824143","data":{"timestamp":" 946906824143"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906825164","data":{"timestamp":" 946906825164"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906826077","data":{"timestamp":" 946906826077"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakaanza kuogelea na kuogelea wakielekea juu kwenye mwangaza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANGAZA"," userResponse":" MWANGAZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906829937","data":{"timestamp":" 946906829935"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOKARIBIA"," userResponse":" WALIPOKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906830389","data":{"timestamp":" 946906830389"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906830614","data":{"timestamp":" 946906830613"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906831399","data":{"timestamp":" 946906831398"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906832800","data":{"timestamp":" 946906832800"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAAJABU"," userResponse":" MAAJABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906834003","data":{"timestamp":" 946906834003"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipokaribia juu ya maji maajabu yalitendeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITENDEKA"," userResponse":" YALITENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906836532","data":{"timestamp":" 946906836531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKIA"," userResponse":" MIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906836887","data":{"timestamp":" 946906836887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906838417","data":{"timestamp":" 946906838414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIGAWIKA"," userResponse":" ILIGAWIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906839241","data":{"timestamp":" 946906839241"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906839838","data":{"timestamp":" 946906839838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906840871","data":{"timestamp":" 946906840871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKAWA"," userResponse":" WAKAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906841137","data":{"timestamp":" 946906841137"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906841799","data":{"timestamp":" 946906841798"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906842270","data":{"timestamp":" 946906842270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906842861","data":{"timestamp":" 946906842861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mikia yao iligawika mara mbili wakawa na miguu yenye vidole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906845129","data":{"timestamp":" 946906845128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906845834","data":{"timestamp":" 946906845834"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONO"," userResponse":" MIKONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906846612","data":{"timestamp":" 946906846611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWILI"," userResponse":" MIWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906846914","data":{"timestamp":" 946906846914"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906847668","data":{"timestamp":" 946906847667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906848816","data":{"timestamp":" 946906848816"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILITOKEA"," userResponse":" ILITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906849436","data":{"timestamp":" 946906849436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906849512","data":{"timestamp":" 946906849512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906850025","data":{"timestamp":" 946906850025"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWA"," userResponse":" VICHWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906850599","data":{"timestamp":" 946906850599"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Na mikono miwili yenye vidole ilitokea chini ya vichwa vyao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAO"," userResponse":" VYAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906853790","data":{"timestamp":" 946906853790"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906854292","data":{"timestamp":" 946906854291"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906854909","data":{"timestamp":" 946906854907"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906855651","data":{"timestamp":" 946906855651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906856354","data":{"timestamp":" 946906856354"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906857597","data":{"timestamp":" 946906857596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIGEUKA"," userResponse":" WALIGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906857801","data":{"timestamp":" 946906857801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906858241","data":{"timestamp":" 946906858240"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906858741","data":{"timestamp":" 946906858741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906858949","data":{"timestamp":" 946906858949"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906859504","data":{"timestamp":" 946906859504"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906862772","data":{"timestamp":" 946906862772"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALITAZAMANA"," userResponse":" WALITAZAMANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906863446","data":{"timestamp":" 946906863446"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906864530","data":{"timestamp":" 946906864530"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPENDANA"," userResponse":" KUPENDANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906865038","data":{"timestamp":" 946906865038"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906865506","data":{"timestamp":" 946906865505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906865742","data":{"timestamp":" 946906865742"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906866230","data":{"timestamp":" 946906866230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walitazamana na kupendana kama mume na mke."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906869629","data":{"timestamp":" 946906869629"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAJENGA"," userResponse":" TUTAJENGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906870189","data":{"timestamp":" 946906870188"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906870709","data":{"timestamp":" 946906870708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906871753","data":{"timestamp":" 946906871753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMANI"," userResponse":" MILIMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906872512","data":{"timestamp":" 946906872512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906873286","data":{"timestamp":" 946906873284"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906875832","data":{"timestamp":" 946906875832"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906876441","data":{"timestamp":" 946906876440"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906877626","data":{"timestamp":" 946906877626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTALIONA"," userResponse":" TUTALIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906878081","data":{"timestamp":" 946906878081"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906879144","data":{"timestamp":" 946906879144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LIKITOKA"," userResponse":" LIKITOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906879719","data":{"timestamp":" 946906879718"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906880756","data":{"timestamp":" 946906880755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFURAHIA"," userResponse":" KUFURAHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906881270","data":{"timestamp":" 946906881270"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906881795","data":{"timestamp":" 946906881794"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila siku tutaliona jua likitoka na kufurahia joto lake."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906883964","data":{"timestamp":" 946906883964"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906884997","data":{"timestamp":" 946906884997"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTALINDA"," userResponse":" TUTALINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906885581","data":{"timestamp":" 946906885581"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906885804","data":{"timestamp":" 946906885804"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906886417","data":{"timestamp":" 946906886417"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MITI"," userResponse":" MITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906887161","data":{"timestamp":" 946906887161"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906888022","data":{"timestamp":" 946906888022"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906890802","data":{"timestamp":" 946906890802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUWA"," userResponse":" TUTAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906891745","data":{"timestamp":" 946906891745"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906891949","data":{"timestamp":" 946906891948"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906892463","data":{"timestamp":" 946906892463"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906892708","data":{"timestamp":" 946906892708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906893438","data":{"timestamp":" 946906893437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa marafiki wa ndege na wanyama."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906896849","data":{"timestamp":" 946906896849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906897453","data":{"timestamp":" 946906897453"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906898275","data":{"timestamp":" 946906898274"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUME"," userResponse":" MUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906898499","data":{"timestamp":" 946906898499"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906899113","data":{"timestamp":" 946906899112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906900084","data":{"timestamp":" 946906900083"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906902627","data":{"timestamp":" 946906902627"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAAM"," userResponse":" NAAM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906903766","data":{"timestamp":" 946906903765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906904034","data":{"timestamp":" 946906904034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKE"," userResponse":" MKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906904225","data":{"timestamp":" 946906904225"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906904857","data":{"timestamp":" 946906904856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906907242","data":{"timestamp":" 946906907241"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906908323","data":{"timestamp":" 946906908322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATEMBEA"," userResponse":" WAKATEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906909165","data":{"timestamp":" 946906909165"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAMOJA"," userResponse":" PAMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906909676","data":{"timestamp":" 946906909675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906910727","data":{"timestamp":" 946906910725"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMWENGU"," userResponse":" ULIMWENGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906911195","data":{"timestamp":" 946906911193"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906911801","data":{"timestamp":" 946906911801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906914433","data":{"timestamp":" 946906914432"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906914556","data":{"timestamp":" 946906914556"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906923728","data":{"timestamp":" 946906923727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906930705","data":{"timestamp":" 946906930705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 3ec26873-0825-4880-9230-34a13a9a6513"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha wakatembea pamoja kwenye ulimwengu wao mpya."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906946322","data":{"timestamp":" 946906946322"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906950430","data":{"timestamp":" 946906950429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906960767","data":{"timestamp":" 946906960767"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906973323","data":{"timestamp":" 946906973323"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906983911","data":{"timestamp":" 946906983911"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" c"," userResponse":" c"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946906990865","data":{"timestamp":" 946906990865"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907006698","data":{"timestamp":" 946907006698"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907019596","data":{"timestamp":" 946907019596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907043672","data":{"timestamp":" 946907043672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_f"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907056969","data":{"timestamp":" 946907056969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907068860","data":{"timestamp":" 946907068860"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907079092","data":{"timestamp":" 946907079092"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907090074","data":{"timestamp":" 946907090074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907102361","data":{"timestamp":" 946907102361"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_k"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907111753","data":{"timestamp":" 946907111753"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_l"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907127020","data":{"timestamp":" 946907127019"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_m"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907141513","data":{"timestamp":" 946907141512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907159141","data":{"timestamp":" 946907159141"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_o"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907172519","data":{"timestamp":" 946907172519"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907179758","data":{"timestamp":" 946907179758"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907182565","data":{"timestamp":" 946907182565"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907190261","data":{"timestamp":" 946907190261"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907200068","data":{"timestamp":" 946907200068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907210522","data":{"timestamp":" 946907210522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907223689","data":{"timestamp":" 946907223689"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907233116","data":{"timestamp":" 946907233115"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_v"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907245330","data":{"timestamp":" 946907245330"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_w"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907254702","data":{"timestamp":" 946907254702"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907256439","data":{"timestamp":" 946907256439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907264553","data":{"timestamp":" 946907264553"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907275074","data":{"timestamp":" 946907275074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.trc:all.asc.A..Z.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907283319","data":{"timestamp":" 946907283318"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" aed570bc-9c5e-4e44-8175-0321257f5ea1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.trc_all.asc.A..Z.10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907295676","data":{"timestamp":" 946907295675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907296276","data":{"timestamp":" 946907296276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907296484","data":{"timestamp":" 946907296484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907296876","data":{"timestamp":" 946907296876"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907298355","data":{"timestamp":" 946907298355"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIONDOKEA"," userResponse":" PALIONDOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907299021","data":{"timestamp":" 946907299020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907299807","data":{"timestamp":" 946907299807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907300926","data":{"timestamp":" 946907300926"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907301625","data":{"timestamp":" 946907301624"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale paliondokea mvulana mmoja aliyeitwa Demane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMANE"," userResponse":" DEMANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907303985","data":{"timestamp":" 946907303984"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907304215","data":{"timestamp":" 946907304214"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907304663","data":{"timestamp":" 946907304663"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PACHA"," userResponse":" PACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907305513","data":{"timestamp":" 946907305512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENZAKE"," userResponse":" MWENZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907306721","data":{"timestamp":" 946907306721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEITWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907307639","data":{"timestamp":" 946907307638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907319715","data":{"timestamp":" 946907319714"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907319804","data":{"timestamp":" 946907319804"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907327651","data":{"timestamp":" 946907327651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907368128","data":{"timestamp":" 946907368127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907376599","data":{"timestamp":" 946907376599"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907393640","data":{"timestamp":" 946907393639"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 1b3d9ea4-c863-44e4-986b-f607146a4063"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907393724","data":{"timestamp":" 946907393724"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 0d047c96-5311-4218-93b3-5b0a2605f05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907399544","data":{"timestamp":" 946907399543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 0d047c96-5311-4218-93b3-5b0a2605f05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907404512","data":{"timestamp":" 946907404512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 0d047c96-5311-4218-93b3-5b0a2605f05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907409086","data":{"timestamp":" 946907409086"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 0d047c96-5311-4218-93b3-5b0a2605f05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907504069","data":{"timestamp":" 946907504060"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 0d047c96-5311-4218-93b3-5b0a2605f05e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Katika bustani ndogo jijini kulikuwa na mti mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907504173","data":{"timestamp":" 946907504173"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7c93b201-f2ad-4e13-9905-23868877c88a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUKIONA"," userResponse":" SIKUKIONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907511928","data":{"timestamp":" 946907511928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7c93b201-f2ad-4e13-9905-23868877c88a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL3.incr.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907518208","data":{"timestamp":" 946907518208"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7c93b201-f2ad-4e13-9905-23868877c88a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907523690","data":{"timestamp":" 946907523690"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7c93b201-f2ad-4e13-9905-23868877c88a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_53","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907738002","data":{"timestamp":" 946907738002"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 7c93b201-f2ad-4e13-9905-23868877c88a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_52"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini sikukiona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907738128","data":{"timestamp":" 946907738127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc:all.asc.A..Z.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907745825","data":{"timestamp":" 946907745825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL2.incr.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907765488","data":{"timestamp":" 946907765488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907780897","data":{"timestamp":" 946907780896"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_54","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907789417","data":{"timestamp":" 946907789417"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907799597","data":{"timestamp":" 946907799597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946907975430","data":{"timestamp":" 946907975429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.24.asc.say.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908028447","data":{"timestamp":" 946908028447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908080391","data":{"timestamp":" 946908080389"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 2f85c37b-2d8d-4ab5-a4ed-517baae27c23"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_53"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mama mama baba alisema kwamba umeenda kumleta mtoto mwingine..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908080635","data":{"timestamp":" 946908080635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 623dc6b3-a3ad-4c9f-af25-0066d35d235f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEMAZANE"," userResponse":" DEMAZANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.128","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908088686","data":{"timestamp":" 946908088684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 623dc6b3-a3ad-4c9f-af25-0066d35d235f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908099037","data":{"timestamp":" 946908099037"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 623dc6b3-a3ad-4c9f-af25-0066d35d235f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908108426","data":{"timestamp":" 946908108425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 623dc6b3-a3ad-4c9f-af25-0066d35d235f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_55"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alikuwa na pacha mwenzake aliyeitwa Demazane."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908180231","data":{"timestamp":" 946908180231"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 5b4738a0-ab47-49cb-83de-606c8ecc26e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908248109","data":{"timestamp":" 946908248109"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 5b4738a0-ab47-49cb-83de-606c8ecc26e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908250855","data":{"timestamp":" 946908250855"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 5b4738a0-ab47-49cb-83de-606c8ecc26e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908306670","data":{"timestamp":" 946908306670"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 5b4738a0-ab47-49cb-83de-606c8ecc26e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908410021","data":{"timestamp":" 946908410021"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 5b4738a0-ab47-49cb-83de-606c8ecc26e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908410153","data":{"timestamp":" 946908410153"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 5b4738a0-ab47-49cb-83de-606c8ecc26e4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka tutakufa walisema kisha wakalia kwa uchungu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SARUJI"," userResponse":" SARUJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908476164","data":{"timestamp":" 946908476163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 085588b8-5273-47d8-b7b8-7bc8e30cd827"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wanyama wengi waliishi pamoja juu ya mti huu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908577264","data":{"timestamp":" 946908577264"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 6bd10d71-5c09-4493-87cc-bd8265f7d7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908585076","data":{"timestamp":" 946908585076"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 6bd10d71-5c09-4493-87cc-bd8265f7d7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908628751","data":{"timestamp":" 946908628751"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 6bd10d71-5c09-4493-87cc-bd8265f7d7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908628935","data":{"timestamp":" 946908628935"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" 6bd10d71-5c09-4493-87cc-bd8265f7d7eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_51"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watu walioishi pale wangehamia nyumba zingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALE"," userResponse":" PALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908686672","data":{"timestamp":" 946908686672"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" d8e18eea-f634-4462-a5c7-71d170631091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908703282","data":{"timestamp":" 946908703281"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" d8e18eea-f634-4462-a5c7-71d170631091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" X"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.ltr.lc.dic:all.asc.A..Z.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946908703676","data":{"timestamp":" 946908703676"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_163226"," gameId":" d8e18eea-f634-4462-a5c7-71d170631091"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.ltr.lc.dic_all.asc.A..Z.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}